{
    "subject": "resource/Michel_Charlin_Tcheumaleu",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Cameroon",
    "human_readable": "Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu was born in Cameroon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9132667183876038,
            "question": "Where was Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8447893857955933,
            "question": "What year was Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7820663452148438,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Cameroon besides Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6497048735618591,
            "question": "What country is Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5513078570365906,
            "question": "What is the significance of being born in Cameroon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5141810178756714,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5078742504119873,
            "question": "Is Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3787679970264435,
            "question": "Does Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu have any notable accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3496197760105133,
            "question": "What is Cameroon known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3056590259075165,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the culture in Cameroon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu was born in Cameroon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8080_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Cameroon known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8080_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu have any notable accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8080_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu known for anything specific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8080_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8080_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Michel Charlin Tcheumaleu was born in Ebolowa, Cameroonian. Therefore, it can be inferred that he was born in Cameroon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}